Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of those visiting and interacting with this website. These terms and conditions explain what to expect on our website when exploring electric fireplaces.

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy. Our policy helps you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us. We want to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site.

What Information Do We Collect?
-------------------------------

When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information. These include personal information you choose to disclose and website use data known as cookies.

1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide:
-----------------------------------------------

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

2\. Make a Wall Look Like Concrete: Website Use Information
-----------------------------------------------------------

Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server log files to collect information about how our site is used. Information may include the date and time of visits, pages viewed and time spent on site.

How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
-----------------------------------------------------

At Electriflames.com, we do not share personally identifiable information or business information with parties except as required by law.

What Are Cookies?
-----------------

A cookie is a very small text document. It often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it. However, (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access its own cookies.

Browsers usually accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may change your browser to refuse cookies. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

IP Addresses
------------

Your computer uses IP addresses every time you are connected to the Internet. Computers in the network use your IP address number to identify your computer. Web servers collect IP addresses automatically as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data.

What About Other Websites Linked to Electriflames?
--------------------------------------------------

We are not responsible for the information or practices employed by sites linked to or from our website. Often links to other websites point to useful information for our site users.

When you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer effective. Your browsing and interaction on any other website is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Therefore, please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

Affiliate Disclosure:
---------------------

[Electriflames.com](https://www.electriflames.com/) supports itself through third-party sponsorship ads and affiliate program partnerships. This means that when you click on links to websites mentioned on our website, they may or may not result in a commission to this site.

On this site, we write about and include only information on electric fireplaces that we think are useful and worthwhile. This applies whether it be commissionable or not. [Electriflames.com](https://www.electriflames.com/) does not sell any products directly.

In addition, this site is not affiliated with the products and services shown as third party ads (i.e [Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense)) on our web pages.

Policy Modifications
--------------------

Finally, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here. However, we will not use personal information in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

Electric Fireplace Inserts
--------------------------

[

Linear Recessed Electric Fireplace](https://www.electriflames.com/electric-fireplace-insert/napoleon-allure/)  
Different Color Flames + Heat  

Electric Fireplace & Mantel
---------------------------

[

Real Flame Electric Fireplace & Mantel](https://www.electriflames.com/fireplace-mantel/real-flame-aspen-electric-fireplace/)  
Easy, Low Cost Installation  

Electric Fireplace TV Stand
---------------------------

[

Modern Fireplace + TV Stand](https://www.electriflames.com/electric-fireplace-tv-stand/)  
\+ Storage for Under $350!  

[

Duraflame Electric Log Set](https://amzn.to/3TdkhVc)  
Use in Your Existing Fireplace!  

Search for:  

Electric Fireplace Tips:
------------------------

* [7 Must-Have Features for Choosing a 3D Flame Electric Fireplace](https://www.electriflames.com/buy/3d-flame-electric-fireplace/)
* [6 Features to Look for in an Energy Efficient Electric Fireplace](https://www.electriflames.com/buy/energy-efficient-electric-fireplace/)
* [5 Key Features for Choosing a Fake Fireplace for Your Apartment](https://www.electriflames.com/portable/fake-fireplace-for-apartment/)

3-Sided Electric Fireplaces
---------------------------

[

Realistic Flames & 3-Dimensional Design](https://www.electriflames.com/review/3-sided-glass-electric-fireplace/)  
Upscale Style, Affordable Install

Farmhouse-Style Fireplace Cabinet
---------------------------------

[

Farmhouse Electric Fireplace](https://www.electriflames.com/tv-stand/farmhouse-electric-fireplace/)  
Storage, TV Stand & Plugs into Wall

Electric Fireplace & Mantel
---------------------------

[

Real Flame Electric Fireplace & Mantel](https://www.electriflames.com/fireplace-mantel/real-flame-aspen-electric-fireplace/)  
Easy, Low Cost Installation

© 2015-2024 [ElectriFlames](https://www.electriflames.com/) - Electric Fireplaces, Log Inserts & Freestanding Fireplace Stove Heaters  
[FAQ](https://www.electriflames.com/buy/electric-fireplace/) | [Contact Us](https://www.electriflames.com/contact-us/) | [Terms of Service](https://www.electriflames.com/privacy-policy/) | As an Amazon Affiliate we earn from qualifying purchases.
